bludot.com 2019-12-14

# Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting the Privacy Policy for Blu Dot Design & Manufacturing, Inc.’s (“Blu Dot”). Your privacy is important to us. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to describe the types of information we collect through our web site (“Web Site”), how and when we share that information; your options as for sharing your information; and our practices for protecting that information.   
By accessing or using our Web sites or giving us personally identifiable information you agree to this Privacy Policy and consent to our collection, use, and disclosure of your personally identifiable information as set forth herein. 

Your use of this Web Site is also governed by our Terms of Use.

## What information do we collect and how do we use it?

It is always your choice whether you wish to provide personally identifiable information through this Web Site; however, if you do not provide the requested personally identifiable information, you may not be able to use certain features or functionalities of the Web Site.

We may collect personally identifiable information (for example, your full name, email address, mailing address, telephone number, or credit card number) from you when you voluntarily submit the information to us when you use our Website. We need this information in order to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status, in order to register you as a user of this site or to provide you with services. For instance, we may disclose your personally identifiable information to our third party service providers who provide services such as website hosting, data storage, data analysis, payment processing, order fulfillment, IT services and infrastructure, customer service, email delivery and administration, credit card processing, auditing and other similar services to enable them to provide services to us or on our behalf.

We may also collect personally identifiable information from you if you choose to subscribe to our email program, catalog mailing list, enter the information into the shopping cart, or participate in sweepstakes, contests, and surveys, or in connection with content or suggestions you post on this Web Site. We also collect non-personally identifiable information (for example, interests, lifestyle choices, opinions) from you when you choose to provide or post non-personally identifiable information on this web site, or via participation in our email program, sweepstakes, contests, surveys or content or suggestions you post on this site.

Non-personally identifiable information may also be collected from you by means of Cookies and Pixel Tags. Cookies are small bits of information that this web site places on your computer. We and our third party service providers use cookies and Pixel Tags to identify your IP address, browser type, domain name, and specific web pages through which you click. This data is collected automatically and utilized to help us look for trends to improve our Web Site and your interactive experience. The cookies that are configured by this Web Site do not contain any personally identifying information, such as your name, or sensitive information, such as your credit card number.

We may also collect your email address via cookies and pixels on the Website through the use of trusted third party partners. These partners may also combine your email information with other information they have access to such as mailing address so that we may serve relevant marketing offers to you via email and direct mail. If you do not want us to use your information this way, please see the choices for opting out of such communications below.

When Blu Dot conducts contests, sweepstakes, promotions and surveys, or joins with other companies to do so, if you choose to participate you may be asked to provide personal information. Blu Dot and the other participating companies may use this information for such purposes as notifying winners and fulfilling promotional obligations, and may also cross reference customer databases to identify common customers. Information from these activities may be used to explore future promotional opportunities or fulfill contractual obligations. Even if you have chosen not to receive communications from Blu Dot prior to your participation in a contest, sweepstakes, promotion or survey, you may still receive information from Blu Dot in connection with such activity if you register for or participate in such activity. You may choose not to participate in contests, sweepstakes, promotions or surveys if you do not wish to receive information from Blu Dot or share your information with Blu Dot and the other companies sponsoring such activities.

We may also use your information to contact you about goods and services that may be of interest to you. We may also share your information with unaffiliated third parties for promotional purposes, including the marketing of their products or services provided that you have not opted out of these disclosures. If you do not want us to use your information this way, please see the choices for opting out of such communications below. 

In the event of a sale, merger, corporate reorganization or similar transaction involving some or all of our business, we may share with or transfer your information to the buyer or successor entity. We may also retain a copy of that information.

In addition to the above, we may share your information if required to comply with a law, regulation, court order or legal process, or if we believe it is necessary to share such information with a government entity or to enforce or apply our Terms of Use. We may share information to protect our rights or property or if the rights of any third party are jeopardized.

## Choices for Opt-in and Opt-out

We and/or our third party marketing partners may contact you and market to you, including by mail, Internet connection, text, telephone, fax or email, consistent with this Privacy Policy. However, in each of our email and texting marketing communications, we will allow you to opt out of future mail and texting marketing communications. Participation in certain of our programs will require you to accept email communications regarding the program itself. You may opt-out of receiving email and texting communications by clicking the "Unsubscribe" link at the bottom of the email or text message received. It may take us up to ten (10) days to complete this process, as permitted by law.

We may use the services of third parties to collect and use anonymous information about your visits to and interactions with our website through the use of technologies such as cookies to personalize advertisements for goods and services. To learn more, or to opt-out of receiving online display advertisements tailored to your interests by our third party partners, visit the Network Advertising Initiative at [www.networkadvertising.org/choices](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices). We may also use technologies, such as our own cookies, to provide you with personalized online display advertising tailored to your interests. To opt out of our cookies used for this online advertising, click here. If you choose to opt-out of cookies or similar technologies, some or all of the features, functionality and promotions available through the Web Site may not be available to you.

We will try to comply with your request(s) as soon as reasonably practicable. Please note that if you opt-out as described above, we will not be able to remove your personally identifiable information from the databases of our third party marketing partners or other third parties with which we have already shared your personally identifiable information as of the date that we implement your opt-out request. Please also note that if you do opt-out of receiving marketing-related messages from us, we may still send important administrative messages to you, and you cannot opt-out from receiving such administrative messages. For example, when you place an order, we will continue to confirm your order and shipment status by email. We may also need to contact you via telephone, email or postal mail with information or questions regarding your order.

## Aggregated Information

We and our service providers may aggregate personally identifiable information collected from our customers and potential customers, for example by using personally identifiable information to calculate the percentage of such individuals who have a particular telephone area code. Aggregated personally identifiable information does not personally identify you or any other customer or potential customer, and such aggregated personally identifiable information is an asset of ours and belongs to us.

## Security

We use reasonable efforts to protect our customers' information.   
When our registration/order form asks customers to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.   
The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for accessing the Web Site, you are responsible for keeping such password confidential. If you are sharing information in public areas, like message boards, we urge you to be careful about the type of information you provide as it may be viewed by any user of the Web Site.

The transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we use reasonable efforts to protect your personally identifiable information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personally identifiable information transmitted to our Web Site. Any transmission of personally identifiable information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on this Web Site.

If you have any questions about the security at our website, please contact us using the information below in the Contact Information section.

##  What about privacy on other sites?

Our Web Site may contain links to other web sites. We provide these links for your convenience, but we do not review, control or monitor the privacy practices of web sites operated by others. We are not responsible for the performance of these sites or for your business dealings with them. Your use of other web sites is subject to the terms and conditions of those web sites, including the privacy policies of those web sites.

If you are visiting our Web site through a link from another web site or search engine, information about your visit to us may be collected by the provider of the other web site or search engine. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of these other web sites or search engines.

## Privacy Policy Changes

We may change this Privacy Policy at any time. If we change this Privacy Policy, we will post the updated Policy on our Web site. You may wish to check this section of our Web site from time to time. Your continued use of our Web Site after we post the updated Privacy Policy is deemed to be acceptance of our changes.

## Children’s Privacy

Our Web Site is not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any information to or on the Web Site. We do not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children younger than the age of thirteen (13) on the Web Sites and we will delete any personally identifiable information later determined to be from a user younger than thirteen (13). If you believe we might have information from or about a child under 13, please contact us using the Contact Information below.

## California Privacy Rights

Pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, residents of California have the right to request from a business, with whom the California resident has an established business relationship, certain information with respect to the types of personally identifiable information the business shares with third parties for direct marketing purposes by such third party and the identities of the third parties with whom the business has shared such information during the immediately preceding calendar year.

To request a copy of the information disclosure provided by Blu Dot pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, please contact us using the Contact Information below.

## Accessing and Correcting Information

You can review and change your personally identifiable information by logging into the Web Site and visiting your account profile page.

## Contact Information

If you have questions or comments about our Privacy Policy or Terms of Use, please contact us via email at [service@bludot.com](mailto:service@bludot.com) or phone at 844.425.8368.
